{
    "id": "b6f77312ef8b4b09a05d7a0293ccdeeb",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Sam hasn’t returned the razor ………………………….. borrowed from ………………………",
            "description": "A pronoun used as a subject should be in its subject form and object should be in its object form. ",
            "answers": [
                "he, me",
                "he, I",
                "him, me"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "232cc852754c47aba6af8182b32d73c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are you doing in ……………………………. room?",
            "description": "The possessive forms of pronouns are - my, mine, his, her, hers, their, theirs, your and yours.",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "me",
                "I"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4da00c8b4b6542acae4ded72c7539cf4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why is ………………………….. so angry today?",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the subject should be in its subject forms. Subject pronouns are: he, she, they, you, we and it.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "26dace0dd8e24aa097b5a4c205d25e16"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know what happened to ……………………………",
            "description": "A pronoun used as the object of a preposition should be in its object form. Examples are: her, him, me, you, them and us.",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6c1267213eab4061964ce0009c25244a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t recognize ……………………. but ……………………. recognized …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her, she, I",
                "she, her, me",
                "her, she, me"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b4c1a974af8242fda0704e4fcee0ee87"
        },
        {
            "question": "It took ……………………………. quite some time to realize what ……………………… was doing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I, me",
                "me, I",
                "me, me"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0a8b4fd91cd84a4189cb260de024b72d"
        },
        {
            "question": "They have never invited ………………………… to ………………………. parties.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "us, their",
                "we, their",
                "us, theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eac16caad3154a3ebed808badf31c374"
        },
        {
            "question": "I expected ………………………… to arrive but ………………………. didn’t.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he, he",
                "him, he",
                "him, him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c9bd770d6b784b57871bd86a8ed37e80"
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked …………………………… what ………………………. problem was.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he, him",
                "him, his",
                "he, him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "22cecf36aaf940c58103eefa351bca68"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should have invited ………………………………",
            "description": "Here the pronoun them is the object of the verb invited. Them is the object form of they. ",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c2bbe8de892945e3bac66bc1cda9fafa"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know ………………………… personally.",
            "description": "Her is the object form of she.",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d42d8f835dd64246a80ba4bb7c869ed6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you do …………………………. a favour?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "we"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f2858402bb604e67896db5d165c8e7f8"
        }
    ]
}